<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Starting on Darul Hadeeth School For Islamic Studies</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/starting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Starting on Darul Hadeeth School For Islamic Studies</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/starting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Daruul Hadeeth Opens</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2015/06/24/masjidopens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2015/06/24/masjidopens/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;grand-opening-of-our-school-and-masjid&#34;&gt;Grand Opening of Our School and Masjid&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are delighted to announce the &lt;strong&gt;official opening&lt;/strong&gt; of our Islamic school and masjid! This momentous occasion marks the beginning of a new chapter in providing &lt;strong&gt;faith-based education&lt;/strong&gt; and a spiritual home for our community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-event&#34;&gt;The Event&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The grand opening ceremony will be a celebration of &lt;strong&gt;learning, faith, and community&lt;/strong&gt;, bringing together students, parents, staff, and local leaders. Attendees will experience:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ribbon-Cutting Ceremony&lt;/strong&gt;: Official inauguration of the school and masjid&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guided Tours&lt;/strong&gt;: Explore classrooms, facilities, and the masjid prayer hall&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speeches &amp;amp; Dedications&lt;/strong&gt;: Inspirational talks from the principal, community leaders, and guest scholars&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Student Performances&lt;/strong&gt;: Qur’an recitations, nasheeds, and cultural presentations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Iftar (during Ramadan)&lt;/strong&gt;: Join us for a shared meal if the event falls in the holy month&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-vision&#34;&gt;Our Vision&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The opening of the school and masjid embodies our mission to:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
