<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Darul Hadeeth School For Islamic Studies</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Darul Hadeeth School For Islamic Studies</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 21:29:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Website Launch</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2021/08/01/sitelaunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2021/08/01/sitelaunch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;exciting-news-our-new-school-website-is-live&#34;&gt;Exciting News: Our New School Website is Live!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to announce the launch of our brand-new school website! This marks a significant milestone in our commitment to &lt;strong&gt;connect with our students, families, and community&lt;/strong&gt; in a more meaningful way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-you-can-explore&#34;&gt;What You Can Explore&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our new website is designed to be &lt;strong&gt;user-friendly, informative, and engaging&lt;/strong&gt;, providing easy access to all the resources you need:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Us:&lt;/strong&gt; Learn about our mission, vision, values, and the principles that guide our school.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Curriculum &amp;amp; Programs:&lt;/strong&gt; Explore the academic and extracurricular programs designed to nurture both &lt;strong&gt;knowledge and character&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Admissions &amp;amp; Apply Now:&lt;/strong&gt; Step-by-step guidance for joining our school, including application forms, fees, and financial aid information.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salah Times:&lt;/strong&gt; Daily prayer schedules for our masjid, following the Africa/Accra timezone.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Islamic Events:&lt;/strong&gt; Stay updated on Ramadan, Eid, and other special community programs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Engagement:&lt;/strong&gt; Discover how students, families, and staff collaborate on service initiatives.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Staff &amp;amp; Leadership:&lt;/strong&gt; Meet our dedicated team shaping the next generation of learners.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-this-matters&#34;&gt;Why This Matters&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We wanted a platform that is not just &lt;strong&gt;informational&lt;/strong&gt; but also &lt;strong&gt;interactive&lt;/strong&gt;, bringing our community closer together. Through this website, parents, students, and visitors can:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daruul Hadeeth Opens</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/2015/06/24/masjidopens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/2015/06/24/masjidopens/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;grand-opening-of-our-school-and-masjid&#34;&gt;Grand Opening of Our School and Masjid&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are delighted to announce the &lt;strong&gt;official opening&lt;/strong&gt; of our Islamic school and masjid! This momentous occasion marks the beginning of a new chapter in providing &lt;strong&gt;faith-based education&lt;/strong&gt; and a spiritual home for our community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-event&#34;&gt;The Event&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The grand opening ceremony will be a celebration of &lt;strong&gt;learning, faith, and community&lt;/strong&gt;, bringing together students, parents, staff, and local leaders. Attendees will experience:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ribbon-Cutting Ceremony&lt;/strong&gt;: Official inauguration of the school and masjid&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guided Tours&lt;/strong&gt;: Explore classrooms, facilities, and the masjid prayer hall&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speeches &amp;amp; Dedications&lt;/strong&gt;: Inspirational talks from the principal, community leaders, and guest scholars&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Student Performances&lt;/strong&gt;: Qur’an recitations, nasheeds, and cultural presentations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Iftar (during Ramadan)&lt;/strong&gt;: Join us for a shared meal if the event falls in the holy month&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-vision&#34;&gt;Our Vision&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The opening of the school and masjid embodies our mission to:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
